{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_6_84CIJW",
                "player_15_84CIJW",
                "player_11_84CIJW",
                "player_7_84CIJW"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                6,
                15,
                11,
                7
            ],
            "animation": [
                "liedown",
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A female soldier with light skin, wearing a black beanie, tactical vest, black shirt, pants, and boots, with a white scarf and communication gear.",
                "A bald man with medium skin, wearing a brown turtleneck, dark pants, and brown shoes.",
                "A man with short black hair, wearing a white button-up shirt, dark pants, and black shoes. Light skin tone.",
                "A bald man with glasses, dark complexion, wearing a black turtleneck, suit, and shoes"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    9260.549,
                    26734.275,
                    1328.147,
                    0,
                    130.70712850879204,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9302.604,
                    26559.86,
                    1331.585,
                    0,
                    178.72095699655296,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    9067.324,
                    26851.838,
                    1339.92,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    9668.533,
                    26940.241,
                    1321.587,
                    0,
                    74.74722391967188,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            9573.824,
            26689.562,
            1321.674
        ],
        "sample_radius": 732.2799724487096
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            9825.044,
            25967.83,
            1322.138,
            0,
            121.9031014433194,
            0
        ],
        [
            8696.122,
            26664.617,
            1385.865,
            0,
            9.653383572240722,
            0
        ],
        [
            9968.507,
            27022.516,
            1327.407,
            0,
            -158.7019470378079,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_black_vest, the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants, the_man_in_white_shirt or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_white_shirt",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_white_shirt"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_brown_sweater_and_black_pants"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_white_shirt, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_bald_man_in_glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_bald_man_in_glasses"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_bald_man_in_glasses, the_woman_in_black_vest or the_man_in_white_shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_woman_in_black_vest",
                    "B. the_man_in_white_shirt"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_woman_in_black_vest"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individuals are present in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many people are in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many men can be observed in the scene?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many humans visible are bald?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many individuals are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many bald men are in the scene?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "How many men are not wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "How many bald individuals are also wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman wearing a black tactical vest?",
                "options": [
                    "A. liedown",
                    "B. standing",
                    "C. sitting",
                    "D. running"
                ],
                "answer": "A. liedown"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man wearing a brown turtleneck?",
                "options": [
                    "A. standing",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. walking",
                    "D. sitting"
                ],
                "answer": "B. crouch"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the white button-up shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. hold something",
                    "B. wave",
                    "C. point",
                    "D. talk"
                ],
                "answer": "A. hold something"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the bald man with glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. walk",
                    "B. sit",
                    "C. stand",
                    "D. jump"
                ],
                "answer": "C. stand"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the right of",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "A. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the front-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-right of"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the bald man in brown sweater and black pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. To the back-left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the back-left of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in glasses relative to the man in white shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. Behind",
                    "B. To the left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. In front of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the right of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in black vest relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. In front of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the bald man in brown sweater and black pants relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the right of",
                    "D. Behind"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in white shirt relative to the bald man in glasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            }
        }
    }
}